so now that we have seen two policies
that try to approximate LRU replacement
let's see if we understood how NMR you
works suppose we have a fully
associative cache with only four lines
and it's using NMR you replacement
starts out empty none of the lines
contain any blocks and suppose that the
processor accesses blocks in the
following order it accesses something in
block a then again something in block a
then something in block B then something
in block a then something in Block C
then something in block a then something
in block D then something in block a
then something in block e ay ay ay ay
and finally something in block B the
question for you what's the smallest
number of cache misses we will have on
the sequence of accesses and what's the
largest number of cache misses that we
might have on these accesses